<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Skg Guide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="name_object">locationName</string>
    <string name="address_object">locationAddress</string>
    <string name="desc_object">locationDescription</string>
    <string name="image_object">locationImage</string>
    <string name="website_object">locationWebsite</string>
    <string name="coordinates_object">locationCoordinates</string>
    <string name="phone_object">phoneNumber</string>
    <string name="working_hours_object">workingHours</string>

    <string name="image_info">Image</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="info_text">INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="additional_info">ADDITIONAL</string>

    <string name="name_text_view">Name of the Place</string>
    <string name="address_text_view">Address of the place</string>
    <string name="website_text_view">Website of the Place</string>
    <string name="phone_text_view">Phone number</string>
    <string name="hours_text_view">Working Hours</string>


    <!-- Sightseeing -->
    <string name="white_tower">White Tower</string>
    <string name="white_tower_address">Thessaloniki 54621</string>
    <string name="white_tower_info">
        Thessaloniki\’s symbol, the White Tower is a 15th century
        fortification which was part of the city’s defenses. \n
        The White Tower is the point where the seaward defense and the eastern wall met. \n
        For years it served as a prison for condemned prisoners awaiting execution. In early 1980s
        it was reconstructed and since 1985 is operating as a museum.  Today the White Tower is used
        as a place of exhibition of the Byzantine Museum of Thessaloniki. For the first months of 2002
        it housed ‘Byzantine Hours’, an exhibition devoted to ordinary life in Byzantine times.\n
        The first floor was presenting the “Professionals in the market place “ which actually is a
        presentation of tools and other objects belonging to goldsmiths, blade-smiths, glassmakers
        and tillers together with coins and a miniature model of Thessaloniki’s market place.\n
        The second floor was devoted to journeys and trade. Objects and texts related to journeys
        by sea and overland, fairs, spectacles and pilgrimages.\n
        The third floor is a presentation of the Byzantine home and its interior design, the
        decoration, supper, and the neighborhood.\n
        At the floor above there was an exhibition of life at home with garments and footwear,
        cosmetics, perfume and jewellery, personal grooming, and even superstitions.\n
        The theme of the top floor was covering burial and funerary customs.
    </string>
    <string name="white_tower_website">http://site.lpth.gr/</string>
    <string name="white_tower_coord">40.626335, 22.948628</string>
    <string name="white_tower_phone">+30 231 026 7832</string>
    <string name="white_tower_working_hours">Mon &#8211; Fri: 08:30 &#8211; 15:00</string>

    <!-- Museums -->
    <string name="archaeological_museum">Archaeological Museum</string>
    <string name="archaeological_address">Manoli Andronikou 6, Thessaloniki 546 21</string>
    <string name="archaeological_museum_info">
        The Archaeological Museum of Thessaloniki opened its doors to the public in 1962 by hosting
        findings from the area of Thessaloniki and the neighboring counties.\n
        The Archaeological Museum of Thessaloniki opened its doors to the public in 1962 by hosting
        findings from the area of Thessaloniki and the neighboring counties.\n
        The museum presents exhibits of the culture of Macedonia from prehistoric times and thereafter.\n
        The museum redesigned the interior area for a better and much more modern presentation of
        the permanent and temporary collections.\n
        Visitors have the opportunity to walk around the five sections of the new structure of the
        museum, through which they come into contact with the culture and people of ancient Macedonia.\n
        The five sections of the Archaeological Museum of Thessaloniki:\n
        Section A: Prehistoric Macedonia.\n
        Presentation of parts of the skull cast of an early hominid the \“Macedonian Ape\” and
        presentation of a copy of the famous skull of Petralona Cave(200,000 BC).\n
        Section-B: To the birth of cities.\n
        Presentation of evidence for the existence of settlements and cemeteries from the region
        extending between Athos and Olympus mountains, during the Iron Age (1100 - 700 BC).\n
        Section C: Macedonia from the 7th century BC to late Antiquity.\n
        Presentation of the life of the Macedonians from the creation of their independent kingdom
        of Macedonia (the ancient years) until the imperial period (1st to 4th century AD)
        when Macedonia was a province of the Roman Empire.\n
        Section D: Thessaloniki, the Macedonian Metropolis\n
        Presentation of historical and archaeological information of the city.  The period from the
        year of its foundation, in 315 BC until the Roman occupation.\n
        Section E: The Gold of the Macedonians.\n
        Presentation of the art of the goldsmiths and exceptional exhibits from various places,
        mostly from cemeteries of Archaic and Classical periods.\n
        The museum also has a chronological narration commencing with the \"Prehistoric Macedonia.\"\n
    </string>
    <string name="archaeological_website">https://www.amth.gr/en</string>
    <string name="archaeological_coord">40.625196, 22.953828</string>
    <string name="archaeological_phone">+30 231 331 0201</string>
    <string name="archaeological_working_hours">Mon &#8211; Fri: 08:00 &#8211; 20:00</string>

    <!-- Restaurants -->
    <string name="molyvos">Molyvos</string>
    <string name="molyvos_address">I.Dragoumi 31, Thessaloniki 54627</string>
    <string name="molyvos_info">
        Molyvos, the idea, the pholosophy, the creation \n
        Finished summers in Mytilini, the tea spoon cake in the homonymous architecture of Molyvos.
        The memories of the group made the dream a reality. And with the boat of the line he took a
        harbor on Idragoud 31 at the first floor of a magnificent neoclassical building.\n
        The feel of Mytilene is faithfully depicted in every corner of the restaurant called Molyvos
        with the handmade wooden furniture, the stone-made iron utensils, the painted ceilings, the
        large island sofas and of course the 9 balloons with the small olive groves, the hungry
        kumarias and the flower beds filled with miniatures , Thyms, basilicas are reborn in the
        center of Thessaloniki in the Island of Molyvos.\n
        The Molyvos Restaurant unleashes the senses with flavors and aromas of the city and the
        East with Aegean and Mediterranean flavors.\n
        In Molyvos, we created our own cell, which was created with the same materials that were
        built in 1930. Roofing over 40 different faces and tsipouro from all over Greece, scattering
        in the space a delightful scent of lifting. Wines are also kept from small vineyards and
        vineyards, as well as composts and tarsi all made by us.\n
        People who are slaves of the clock, the time and the machine who do not have to think, love,
        feel the great joy of life, should ever come to places like Molyvos that say here and time
        stops and Life It proceeds with a very quiet and serene rhythm.\n
    </string>
    <string name="molyvos_website">https://molyvos.gr/</string>
    <string name="molyvos_coord">40.636604,22.940037</string>
    <string name="molyvos_phone">+30 231 055 5952</string>
    <string name="molyvos_working_hours">Everyday: 13:00 &#8211; 01:00</string>


    <!-- Coffee bars-->
    <string name="tribeca">TriBeCa All Day Cafe Bar</string>
    <string name="tribeca_address">Leoforos Nikis 19, Thessaloniki 54623</string>
    <string name="tribeca_info">
            Specialties \n
            Serves breakfast, lunch, coffee and drinks\n
            Services \n
            Takes Reservations\n
            Walk-Ins Welcome\n
            Good For Groups\n
            Good For Kids\n
            Take Out\n
            Waiter Service\n
            Outdoor Seating\n
    </string>
    <string name="tribeca_website">https://www.facebook.com/TribecaThessaloniki</string>
    <string name="tribeca_coord">40.6309, 22.9421</string>
    <string name="tribeca_phone">+30 231 022 6604</string>
    <string name="tribeca_working_hours">Everyday: 09:00 &#8211; 03:00</string>
</resources>
